当时大家都很高兴
It was a situation there where everybody was happy...
看到战争接近尾声
...to see the war coming to an end...
而德军也无心作战
...and the Germans didn't really have a heart for it.
他们也感到战争将结束
They realized that the end was there.
我以前说过 唯一的好德军是死掉的德军
We'd say the only good Kraut is a dead one.
可是后来发现他们只是些孩子
But there was something in there that you know, hey that was a kid.
大部分还只是孩子 我们都还是孩子
Most of them were kids. We all were kids.
他们要做的工作跟我一样
They had a job to do the same way as me.
所以我们去把该做的工作做好
So, we went about and did the job that we had to do.
我想我们以为德国人
I think we thought that the Germans...
也许是世上最邪恶的人
...were probably the evilest people in the world.
但是...
But...
当战争持续进行下去
...as the war went along...
我们也发现并不是德国人本身的问题
...we found out also that it wasn't the Germans, per se.
很多...他们的士兵
A lot of those soldiers...
我常常这么想
I've thought about this often.
有些人可能可以成为好友
That man and I might've been friends.
我们可能有很多共同之处
We might have had a lot in common.
你知道 他也许喜欢钓鱼
He might have liked to fish, you know.
他也许喜欢打猎
He might have liked to hunt.
这很难说的
You never know, you know.
当然 他们只是在尽职做事
They were doing what they were supposed to do.
而我也只是在做我该做的事
And I was trying to do what I was supposed to do.
可是在不同的情境下
But, under different circumstances...
我们可能成为好朋友
...we might have been good friends.
美国家庭影院 出品
联合制作: 梦工厂 与 PLAYTON公司
领衔主演:埃奥恩・贝利 迈克尔・库德利兹 戴尔・戴伊
里克・格梅兹 斯科特・格里米斯 达米安・路易斯
朗・利文斯通 詹姆斯・马迪奥 罗斯・麦考尔
马泰・塞特尔 道格拉斯・斯佩恩 唐尼尔・贝里
角色的分派: 利伯曼/巴顿
视觉效果总监:安格斯・ 比克尔顿
特殊效果监督员: 乔斯・威廉姆斯
服装设计师: 安娜・谢帕德
编辑: 弗朗西斯・ 帕克
音乐: 迈克尔・凯曼
制作设计 : 安东尼・布拉特
摄影指导: 雷米・阿德法拉欣
监督指导: 艾力克・简得森
制作人: 玛丽・理查兹
监督制片人: 埃里克・ 柏克
联合执行制片人: 史蒂芬・安布洛斯 加里・高依兹曼 托尼・ 托
执行制片人: 汤姆・ 汉克斯 斯蒂文・ 斯皮尔伯格
兄弟连作者: 史蒂芬・安布洛斯
编剧:约翰・奥尔洛夫
导演:戴维・弗兰克尔
兄 弟 连
第九集
为 何 而 战
( 1945年4月11日 )
(德国 塔兰 )
那边
That way.
我告诉你德国人的一个特色
Tell you one thing about the Krauts:
他们真会清理东西
They sure clean up good.
是啊 只需要给他们一点莫扎特就行了
Yeah, all you need's a little Mozart.
贝多芬
Beethoven.
你说什么 长官?
Sorry, sir?
那不是莫扎特
That's not Mozart.
那是贝多芬
That's Beethoven.
一个月前
德国史徒佐堡
快过来 鸡崽
Come on, chicken.
有了 这只有一些 乔治
All right, this one's got some, George.
你...
You...
你抓住鸡 我来拿蛋
You grab the chicken and I'm gonna grab the eggs.
好 没问题
Great, all right.
你抓住它的脚
Just grab him by the foot.
快过来 鸡崽
Come on, chicken.
好吧 如果它咬我的话...
All right, If this thing bites me...
法兰克 我发誓我会毙了他
...Frank, I swear I'll shoot it.
嗨 你好吗?
Guten Tag, Fraulein.
你好...
Guten Tag.
等一下!
Hold on! Hold...
喂 乔治
But, George...
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
等我一下
Hold on a second, hold on.
嘿 别这样
Hey, hey, come on.
我只是想和你说说话
I just wanna talk to you.
I just wanna talk to you, that's all, I just wanna talk.
看我有什么? 巧克力棒?
Okay, look what I got. Chocolate bar?
你喜欢吗? 你喜欢巧克力吗?
You like that? You like chocolate?
鲁兹 你别去烦她好吗?
Hey, Luz, why don't you leave her alone?
法兰克 你别来烦我好吗?
Frank, why don't you just leave me alone, okay?
你不喜欢巧克力吗?
You don't like chocolate?
算了 我也不喜欢巧克力
I don't like it either.
那这个呢? 香烟
How about this? Cigarettes.
骆驼牌的
Camel?
你喜欢这个 对不对?
Yeah, you like that?
够了 鲁兹
Come on, Luz.
法兰克 拜托你去弄你的炒蛋好吗?
Frank, please, why don't you go make your omelet?
我一点蛋都不会分给你的 你这个笨蛋
Well, you ain't getting none of my eggs, blockhead.
老天 我朋友真爱说话
Jesus, my friend just keeps talking.
拿去 我有两包
Here, I got two packs here.
拿给你的朋友之类的
Give it to your friends or something.
你干吗不过来坐下?
Why don't you come and sit down?
要不要坐下来?
Wanna sit down?
这里?
Here?
来吧 就是这样
Come on, that's it.
法兰克! 等等...
Hey, Frank, hold on.
派康提! 别这样
Perc, Jesus, come on.
怎么啦?
What?
那不是尼克森上尉吗?
That Captain Nixon?
我想是的
I think so.
他带着伞具做什么?
What the hell's he doing in his harness?
不知道
I don't know.
也许我们跳伞到了柏林 战争就已经结束了
Maybe we jumped into Berlin, the war's over.
结果怎么样?
So, what happened?
没泡到德国小妞?
No dice with the Fraulein?
她赏了我一巴掌
No dice. She smacked me in the mouth.
虽然这样
Tell you what, though.
我觉得德国看来会变成蛮亲善的地方
Germany's looking to be pretty good fraternizing territory, huh?
你的香烟呢?
Did you lose your cigarettes?
上帝啊
Oh, God.
上帝
God, ja, ja, ja.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
等等
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
没错 就是这样 太棒了
That's right, yeah.
杰诺维克!
Janovec!
糟了!
Oh, shit!
长官
Sir.
我的东西呢?
Where's my stuff?
我把它放在那边了 长官
I thought I'd leave it over there, sir.
那边
Over there.
往这儿走
Here.
多谢
Thanks.
不客气 长官
You're welcome, sir.
长官
Oh, sir.
早上好 长官
'Morning, sir.
早
'Morning.
你有可以放的下这些东西的箱子吗?
You got a box all this stuff will fit into?
我想有的 长官 一样的目的地?
Yes, sir, I think so, same destination?
是的
Yeah.
好的 长官我会确定它明早第一时间寄出去
Yes, sir, I'll make sure it goes out first thing in the morning.
谢谢你
Thank you, Private.
我确定你们这些人都能搜集到一堆东西...
Your folks are gonna have quite a collection by the time you get...
...带回家 长官
...home, sir.
谁找到的就是谁的
Finders keepers.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
尼克?
Nix?
在这里
In here.
你这混蛋
Dog.
当我整早在做补给简报的时候 你却跟第17师进行空降作战?
Making combat jumps with the 17th while I'm in supply briefings all morning.
对 算我好运
Yeah, lucky me.
恭喜你
No, congratulations.
你可能是101师中唯一在伞徽上能别上三颗作战星星的人
You're probably the only man in the 101st with three combat stars over his jump wings.
对一个从未在战斗中开过一枪的人来说 不算太坏吧?
Not bad for someone who's never fired his weapon in combat?
真的吗?
Really?
你真的从来没...
Really, you've never...
没有
No.
在我们经历过的那么多战役中?
Not even with all the action we've seen?
一枪都没有
Not a round.
那么...
So...
你今天早上跳的如何?
How'd it go this morning, the jump?
真不错 棒极了!
It was great, fantastic.
我们在空投区直接被命中
We took a direct hit over the drop zone.
我跳出来了 另外两个也跳了
I got out. Two others got out.
其他的弟兄呢?
The rest of the boys?
他们在德国上空某处爆炸了
Well, they blew up over Germany somewhere.
我很遗憾...
Yeah, I'm sorry.
关于什么?
About what?
这个惨烈的状况发生在...
Well, tough situation for the...
对...那些兄弟
Oh, yeah, the boys, yeah.
真是可怕
It's terrible.
还好不是我
Oh, well, wasn't me.
你知道吗 真正惨的是他们的连长也死了
You know, the real tragedy is they also lost their CO.
所以猜猜看谁该帮他们写信回家?
So guess who gets to write all the letters home.
真是个噩梦
Goddamn nightmare.
今早辛克上校来过
Got a visit from Colonel Sink this morning.
这位好上校如何?
And how is the good colonel?
很关切
Concerned.
你还是只喝"翡特69"的陈年威士忌吗?
Still drinking nothing but the Vat 69?
尼克森太太的宝贝儿子只喝最好的酒
Only the finest for Mrs. Nixon's baby boy.
与团部闹的不愉快吗?
Had a problem up at regiment?
这个吗?
What, this?
他是这么跟你说的吗?
Is that what he said?
没有 我只是不喜欢那里而已
No, I just don't like it up there.
很好!
Good,
那你应该很高兴听到辛克上校要把你降回营部作战官
so you'll be happy to hear that Sink is transferring you back down to Battalion S-3.
你觉得我该写些什么 给这些父母 迪克?
What do you think I should write to these parents, Dick?
你听到我的话了吗 尼克? 你被降级了...
Hear what I said, Nix? You've been demoted.
对 降级 知道了!
Yeah, demoted, got you.
因为我不知道该怎么告诉他们
I don't know how to tell them...
他们的孩子甚至连跳都来不及跳
...their kids never even got out of the plane.
告诉他们你一向告诉他们的
You tell them what you always tell them:
"他们的儿子英勇阵亡"
"Their sons died as heroes."
你还相信那一套?
You really still believe that?
是 我相信
Yeah, I do.
你不信吗?
Don't you?
美国人汇寄协助欧洲行动
"The Cooperative for American Remittance to Europe...
简称为CARE 已经开始在美国本土聚集食品
"...or CARE, has begun assembling food packages stateside...
来帮助那些有迫切需要的欧洲家庭
"...to assist those European families in dire need."
讲起来所有家庭都算是
Which is presumably all of them.
所以感谢你们写信回家
So, notes home to your family reminding them...
提醒他们尽可能的捐款
...to donate whatever they can would be much appreciated.
我确定你们会很高兴知道
I'm sure that you'll be happy to know...
"奥克拉荷马"还在百老汇上演
...Oklahoma's still playing on Broadway.
∮奥克拉荷马的微风吹抚着平原∮
"Oklahoma where the wind comes sweepin' down the plain
∮波浪般的麦穗 闻起来多香甜∮
"And the wavin' wheat can sure smell sweet
∮当阵阵和风∮
"When the wind comes
∮在雨后出现∮
"Right behind the rain"
欧基夫 你坐到刺刀了?
O'Keefe, you were sitting on your bayonet there?
你还是让鲁兹来唱好了
Why don't you leave the singing to Luz?
除非你想表演一段歌舞秀
Hey, unless you wanna do...
欧基夫 给你选一样
...Surrey with the Fringe on Top, O'Keefe.
丽塔海华丝要结婚了
Rita Hayworth's getting married.
丽塔 告诉我这不是真的
Oh, Rita, say it isn't true.
劳莱和哈台...
Abbott and Costello...
战地新闻
Wartime news.
在鲁尔区的反抗瓦解了
"Resistance in the Rhur pocket's crumbling.
看来在雷玛根将有所突破
"It looks like there might be a breakout in Remagen."
显然德军在从战线撤走时忘了炸掉其中一座桥
Apparently the Krauts forgot to blow up a bridge when they headed back over the Rhine.
我想第17空降师的弟兄最后战果还不错
I guess the boys in the 17th Airborne did okay after all.
别提了 要不现在早就攻下柏林了
Forget it, we'd be in Berlin by now, sir...
如果是换我们去的话
...if it was us instead of them?
没错 对!
That's right!
你觉得我们何时才会跳伞到柏林
When do you think we'll jump into Berlin...
见识下真正的战斗?
...see some real action?
你赶时问吗?
You in a rush?
不是
No.
你是不是想捧个国会荣誉勋章回去还是怎么样?
So, you wanna go home with a Congressional Medal of Honor?
没有 我只是想我该问问
I just thought I'd ask.
那麻烦你帮个忙
Well, why don't you do us all a favor?
什么也别想
Don't think.
该死的新兵
Damn replacements.
哈利路亚
Hallelujah.
也该是时候了
'Bout time.
你们应该感到幸运的
Yeah, consider yourselves lucky.
尼克森在发表"当代大事"的演说
Nixon was giving another current events lecture.
告诉我你们这儿风平浪静
So, tell me nothing's happening.
风平浪静
Nothing's happening.
在黎明有几发炮击
Couple of artillery rounds at dawn...
可能是从河对岸打过来的
...probably from across the river, but...
就这样而已
...that's about it.
只是吓了赫胥一跳
It spooked Hashey, though.
给你 派康提 我刚读完
Here, Perco, I just finished it.
是吗? 有没有关于性的情节?
Oh, yeah? Any sex in it?
不是那种书
Ain't that kind of book.
- 回见! - 好 再见!
- See you. - Yeah, see you.
"一株在布鲁克林生长的树"
好 继续前进
Okay, move on.
嘿 欧布安
Hey, O'Brien.
轻点 好吗? 我要看书
Relax, would you? I'm trying to read.
我叫欧基夫
It's O'Keefe.
是吗?
Is that right?
对 帕特里克・欧基夫
Yeah, Patrick O'Keefe.
我的朋友叫我派弟
My friends call me Paddy.
嘿 欧布安
Hey, O'Brien.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
我说过我叫欧基夫
I told you, it's O'Keefe.
你知道为什么没有人记得你的名字?
Do you know why no one remembers your name?
那是因为没有人想要去记你的名字
It's 'cause no one wants to remember your name.
有太多的史密斯...迪马拖...欧基夫...
There's too many Smiths, Dimattos and O'Keefes...
欧布安...来补充托卡尔老爹
...and O'Briens, who show up here replacing Toccoa men...
结果你们这些笨新兵先阵亡
...that you replacements got killed in the first place.
他们都跟你一样笨手笨脚的
And they're all like you. They're all piss and vinegar.
"德军在哪儿? "
"Where are the Krauts at?"
"让我来对付他们"
"Let me at them."
"我什么时候会跳伞到柏林? "
"When will I get to jump into Berlin?"
两天之后 他们倒在地上
Two days later, there they are...
肚破肠流
...with their guts hanging out...
声嘶力竭的叫医护兵
...and they're screaming for a medic.
哭爹喊娘的
Begging for their goddamn mother.
那些笨蛋连他们已经死了都还不知道呢
Them dumb fucks don't even know they're dead yet.
你有在听我说吗?
Hey, are you listening to me?
你知道 这段时期是我在战争中看过最好的部分吗?
Do you get that this is the best part of fucking war I've seen?
我有热餐吃...热水洗...暖和的床!
I got hot chow, hot showers, warm bed.
在德国几乎跟在家一样好
Germany is almost as good as being home.
我今天甚至可以用真的卫生纸擦屁股
I even got to wipe my ass with real toilet paper today.
所以别再问你什么时候可以见识到战斗 好吗?
Quit asking about when you're gonna see some action, will you?
别再唱那首该死的情歌!
And stop with the fucking love songs!
你何时离家的?
When'd you ship out?
几个星期前?
A few weeks ago?
对
Yeah.
我离家已经两年了
It's been two years since I seen home.
两年了
Two years.
这该死的战争
This fucking war.
两次巡逻都没发现德军
Neither patrol found a single Kraut.
这里也没有
There were none here either.
他们现在应该在河对岸
They'll be across the river by now.
让我们派出一支夜巡队
Let's send out a night patrol.
查看下另一头的堤岸
Check out the embankment on the far side.
总统去世了
President's dead.
两对Q说话
Pair of queens bets.
好 赌两块
All right, two bucks.
尼克
Nix.
不 我不跟了
No, I'm out.
好吧
All right.
我跟你
Well, I'll call you two...
再加两块
...and I'll raise you another two.
我不信我们不跳伞到柏林了
I can't believe we're not gonna drop into Berlin.
没错
No shit.
艾森豪威尔要让俄国佬占领它
Ike's gonna let the Russkies have it.
俄国佬
Russkies.
他妈的
God damn it.
我跟你说吧：
Let me tell you something:
这场战争已经无关战斗了
This war is not about fighting anymore.
现在是看谁占领了什么
It's about who gets what.
你们下一把再发牌给我
Why don't you deal me out of the next hand?
你的钱呢?
What about your money?
我们又要等他吗?
Are we waiting on him again?
对
Yep.
该死的杂货店
Goddamn drugstore.
长官
Sir.
嘿 伙计 等一下
Hey, guys, wait up.
嘿 戴克斯特 你好吗?
Hey, Dexter, how you doing?
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
知道那是谁吗?
You know who that was?
不知道
No.
早安
'Morning.
尼克森上尉
Captain Nixon.
很高兴见到你 长官
Good to see you, sir.
我想我这儿有你的信
I think I have some mail for you.
我本来想下午...
Yeah, I was gonna drop it off this afternoon...
跟第二营其他的信一起给你
...with all the other 2nd Battalion mail.
可是既然你来了
But since you're here...
谢谢
Thanks.
我跟你说 我找不到威士忌
Listen, I'm having some trouble finding some whiskey.
威士忌?
Whiskey?
对 一种特别的牌子
Yeah, a particular brand of whiskey.
翡特69
Vat 69.
完全正确
Exactly right.
老实说 长官
I gotta be honest, sir...
那个牌子在德国很难找到
...that ain't gonna be easy to find in Germany.
这里的选择不多
Pickings are kind of slim here.
对 这我知道
Yeah, don't I know it?
还有如果我真的找到几瓶 长官
And even if I do find some, sir...
它恐怕并不便宜
...it ain't gonna be cheap.
钱不是问题
That won't be a problem.
魏斯特 你听到消息了吗?
Hey, you hear the news?
抱歉 长官 我不知道你在这儿
Sorry, sir. I didn't realize that you were here.
什么消息?
What news?
三十万德军刚刚投降了
300,000 Krauts just surrendered.
三十万?
Three hundred?
对 我们一小时内要出发
Yeah, we're moving out in an hour.
- 一小时? - 是的
- One hour? - Yeah
长官
Sir, sir.
你的信
Your mail.
继续帮我找
Keep looking.
对不起
Excuse me, pardon me.
要出发了 我们走
Get a move on, let's go.
老天 连那只狗?
Jesus Christ, the dog?
路易?
Lew?
凯西要跟我离婚
Cathy's divorcing me.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
她要拿走所有的东西
She's taking everything.
她要拿走房子
She's taking the house...
带走孩子
...taking the kid.
还要把狗带走
She's taking the dog.
那根本不是她的狗!
It's not even her dog!
那是我的狗!
It's my dog!
她要带走我的狗!
She's taking my dog!
我们走 把它们装好 走吧!
Let's go, load them up, come on!
中士 你们这里有什么?
Sarge, what do you have in here?
德国人吗?
Germans?
派康提
Hey, Perconte.
你有打火机吗?
You got a lighter?
没有 长官 我不抽烟
No, sir, I don't smoke.
嘿 我们要去哪里?
Hey, where we headed?
我们要上阿尔卑斯山 打火机给我
To the Alps. Let me see that lighter.
- 阿尔卑斯山? - 对!
- The Alps? - Yeah.
- 它在柏林附近吗? - 不是
- That near Berlin, sir? - No.
那是在巴伐利亚
That's in Bavaria.
国家社会主义(即纳粹)党的发源地
Birthplace of national socialism.
这意思是我们不会跳伞进柏林了?
So, that mean no drop into Berlin?
不会了
No drop into Berlin.
希特勒下令 叫武装党卫军在山区藏洞来驱逐侵略者
Hitler ordered the Waffen SS to hide in the mountains and repel all invaders.
他要他们开始进行本土保卫战
He wants them to start a guerrilla war.
侵略者
Invaders.
听起来挺好的
Damn, I like the sound of that.
他们要战到最后一兵一卒
They'll die the last man trying.
- 长官 - 什么事?
- Sir. - What?
我的打火机
My lighter.
好吧 打火机不错
All right, nice lighter.
谢谢
Thanks.
武装党卫军?
Waffen SS?
看来你的愿望要实现了 欧佛拉内
Looks like you'll get your wish anyway, O'Flannery.
那些人...
Those guys...
根本是疯子
Fucking crazy.
我叫欧基夫
It's O'Keefe.
∮他不需要再跳了∮
"He ain't gonna jump no more
∮碧血如泉 取义成仁∮
"Gory, gory, what a hell of a way to die
∮他不需要再跳了∮
"He ain't gonna jump no more
∮基督缠绕着他的颈部∮
"Risers wrapped around his neck Connectors cracked his dome
∮围着他的棱骨∮
"Suspension lines were tied in knots Around his skinny bones
∮以天空为幕 他冲向地表∮
"The canopy became the shroud he hurdled to the ground
∮他不需要再跳了∮
"He ain't gonna jump no more
∮碧血如泉 取义成仁∮
"Gory, gory, what a hell of a way to die
"Gory, gory, what a hell of a way to die"
你还好吗 尼克?
You okay, Nix?
好 我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
∮他不需要再跳了∮
"He ain't gonna jump no more"
她痛恨那只狗
She hates that dog.
∮他血流如注∮
"His blood went spurting high
∮他以为自己绝不会取义成仁∮
"His comrades they were heard to say, 'A hell of a way to die'
∮他躺在自己的血泊中∮
"He laid there rolling 'round in the welter of his gore
∮他不用再跳了∮
"He ain't gonna jump no more
∮碧血如泉 取义成仁∮
"Gory, gory, what a hell of a way to die
∮他不用再跳了∮
"He ain't gonna jump no more"
好日子快要来了 韦伯
There's gonna be good times, Web.
我是说在我们回家之后
When we get home, I mean.
我第一件要做的事
First thing I'm gonna do...
是到旧金山找回在出租车公司的工作
...is get my job back at the cab company in Frisco.
赚爆那些返乡水兵的钱
Make a killing off all those sailors coming home, you know?
然后我要找个好犹太女孩
Then I'm gonna find me a nice Jewish girl...
有超大酥胸
...with great big, soft titties...
还有迷人笑容的那种
...and a smile to die for.
把她娶回家
Marry her.
然后我要买栋房子
Then I'm gonna buy a house...
一间有很多房间的大房子
...a big house with lots of bedrooms...
让我们能生一群小李高特
...for all the little Liebgotts we're gonna be making.
她一定会喜欢的
She ought to like that.
杰诺维克 你在看什么?
Hey, Janovec, what you reading?
一篇文章
An article.
真的?
No shit.
有关什么的?
What's it about?
关于我们为何而战
It's about why we're fighting the war.
我们为何而战 杰诺维克?
Why are we fighting the war, Janovec?
看来好象是德国人很坏
It seems that the Germans are bad.
非常坏
Very bad.
还用你说
You don't say.
德国人很坏 不是吗?
The Germans are bad?
嘿 法兰克 这家伙在读的文章
Hey, Frank, this guy's reading an article over here.
说德国人很坏
It says the Germans are bad.
那你呢 韦伯?
So, what about you, Web?
每天都学到新事物 对吧?
You learn something new every day?
我要先完成学业 然后...
I guess I'll finish school first and then...
等一下 完成学业?
Wait a minute, finish school?
你是说你老是哈佛长哈佛短的
You mean all this time you've been talking about Harvard this...
结果你根本没毕业?
...and Harvard that, and you ain't even finished?
我只有这件事没提
For one thing I haven't told you anything.
对 我是没有毕业
Yes, yes, I haven't finished.
那又怎样?
So the fuck what?
好 我们暂时别谈这个话题
All right, Web, breathe a little. Jesus.
见鬼
Fuck.
因为你老是讲的好象是 你知道
It's just the way you always talked, you know?
我们都以为...
We all figured that...
你知道吗? 你说的对
Hey, you know, you're right.
没毕业又怎样?
So the fuck what?
那你念的是什么?
So, what did you study?
文学
Literature.
别开玩笑了
Get out of here.
真的吗?
You serious?
我也爱看书
I love to read.
是吗?
Do you?
迪克崔西 闪电侠
Dick Tracy, Flash Gordon mostly.
对 又怎样呢?
Yeah, fuck.
"正进入敌人领土 提高警觉"
告诉她她只有五分钟
Tell her she's got five minutes.
出去 出去
Raus, raus.
长官 她说她们无处可去
Sir, she says they've got nowhere to go...
而隔壁又是...
...but the house next door is...
嘿 你们听到了吗?
Hey, hey, do you hear this?
这家伙说他不是纳粹
He says he ain't a Nazi.
为什么我到了德国却还没遇上一个纳粹?
Why haven't I met a Nazi yet in all of Germany?
我们只在这儿待一晚
We're only gonna be here one night.
你还有四分钟
You've got four minutes.
出去
Raus.
快点
Come on.
快走!
Let's go. Move!
都出去!
All of you, out!
你看他们
Look at them.
就算是战败了 他们还是带着傲气行军
Even in defeat, they still know how to march with pride.
嘿 你!
Hey, you!
没错 就是你这个笨德国杂种!
That's right, you stupid Kraut bastards!
没错!
That's right!
跟福特和通用汽车问好
Say hello to Ford and General fucking Motors.
你们这群笨法西斯猪
You stupid fascist pigs.
看看你们!
Look at you!
你们只有马
You have horses.
你们是怎么想的?
What were you thinking?
够了 韦伯斯特
That's enough, Webster.
别再说了
Give it a rest.
把我们从半个地球外拖来
Dragging our asses half-way around the world...
干扰我们的生活
...interrupting our lives.
为了什么?
For what?
你们这些无知 卑贱的人渣!
You ignorant, servile scum!
我们在这里干什么?
What the fuck are we doing here?
我要派出一些巡逻队
I wanna send out some patrols.
Ｄ连搜索村庄 Ｅ连和Ｆ连搜索树林
We'll have Dog here in the village. Easy and Fox in the woods.
Ｅ连负责西北区 李普少尉
Easy Company's gonna take the northwest. Lt. Lipton...
长官!
Sir.
叫第一、第二排进森林扫荡
Have 1st and 2nd Platoons go to the woods.
叫第三排在外围扫荡
Have 3rd swing around.
是的 长官 泰伯特军士长
Yes, sir. 1st Sergeant Talbert.
你不是担心伏击吧?
You're not worried about an ambush, are you?
不
No.
只是因为我们有可能在这里过夜
Just in case we have to stay here for the night.
- 欧基夫 - 中士
- O'Keefe. - Sarge
你为什么那么紧张 小子?
Why the hell are you so jumpy, boy?
我没有紧张
I'm not jumpy.
我很好
I'm fine.
我大老远就可以听见你的心跳 小子
Can hear your heart pounding in Arkansas, boy.
你别再逗他了 大牛
Jesus Christ, give the kid a break, Bull.
乔治
Hey, George.
什么?
Yeah?
这有没有让你想起巴斯通?
Does this kind of remind you of Bastogne?
有 你说我才想起来
Yeah, now that you mention it.
除了这里没有雪
Except, of course, there's no snow...
我们有热餐吃
...we got warm grub in our bellies...
而且树干没被老德轰的七零八落
...and the trees aren't fucking exploding from Kraut artillery.
对! 法兰克 除此之外...
But, yeah, Frank, other than that...
这里很象巴斯通
...it's a lot like Bastogne.
对
Right.
大牛 帮我赏他一巴掌
Bull, smack him for me, please.
谢谢你
Thank you.
有人吗?
Hello?
这里真是安静
It sure is quiet.
他说的对 各位
He is right, fellows.
- 看到佛利没有? - 没有!
- You seen Foley? - No.
嘿 伙计
Hey, guys.
有人看到任何军官吗?
Any of you see any of the officers?
- 没有 去问问普派 - 嘿 普派
- No, speak to Popeye. - Hey Pop.
普派 你看到哪个军官吗? 尼克森? 佛利?
Popeye, you seen any officers? Nixon, Foley?
史毕尔在沿街搜索建筑物
Speirs is searching them buildings right down the street.
什么事?
What's the matter?
摩尔 你有看到任何军官吗?
More, have you seen any of the officers?
有 温特斯少校就在里面
Yeah, Major Winters is right in there.
你还好吗 法兰克?
Are you all right, Frank?
温特斯少校 长官
Major Winters, sir.
我们发现了些东西
We found something.
我们在执行巡逻任务 然后 我们发现了这个...
We're out on patrol and we came across this...
什么...? 法兰克 发现了什么?
What, what, what? Frank, Frank, what is it?
我不知道 长官
I don't know, sir.
我不知道
I don't know.
少校
Major, sir.
把它打开
Open it up.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
退后
Stand back.
给我们一点空间 退后一点
Give us some room here, stand back.
退后
Back, back.
克里斯登生 你手下谁会说德语?
Christenson, any of your men speak German?
没有 长官
No, sir.
我需要李高特! 李高特!
I need Liebgott. Liebgott!
李普 去找李高特
Lipton, find me Liebgott.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
李高特!
Liebgott, Liebgott!
Liebgott!
少校要你到前面来 马上!
Major needs you up front, right now.
是 长官
Sure.
好了 小伙子们
All right, boys.
这些人需要照顾
These people need care.
给他们水喝 还有多的口粮
Give them water and all spare rations.
去拿些毛毯来 快去!
Grab me some blankets, quick.
我的上帝啊
Oh, my God.
迪克?
Dick?
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
拿去 喝点水
Here, take some water.
老天 韦伯 你相信有这种地方吗?
Jesus, Web, can you believe this place?
不相信
No.
没事了
It's okay.
现在好了
Better now.
他说守卫今早刚离开 长官
He said the guards left this morning, sir.
他们先放火烧了些木屋
They burned some of the huts first...
犯人都还在屋里 长官 活生生的...被烧死
...with the prisoners still in them, sir alive.
我的老天
Jesus Christ.
有些犯人想要阻止他们
Some of the prisoners tried to stop them.
有人就被杀了
Some of them were killed.
他们没有足够子弹杀光所有的犯人
They didn't have enough ammo for all the prisoners, so...
所以他们就尽量的杀
...they killed as many as they could...
在他们离开集中营之前
...before they left the camp.
他们把大门锁上 朝南边走了
They locked the gates behind them and headed south.
镇上一定有人跟他们说我们来了
Someone in town must have told them we were coming.
对 我也这么想
Yeah, I think so.
麻烦你问他...
Will you ask him...
问他这是什么样的营区?
...ask him what kind of camp this is?
什么...
What...
为什么他们在这里?
Why are they here?
他说这是一个劳改集中营
He says it's a work camp for...
专门关押 Unerwunscht?
Unerwunscht?
我不确定这个字的意思 长官
I'm not sure what the word means, sir.
也许是不需要 不喜欢?
Unwanted, disliked maybe?
罪犯?
Criminals?
我想不是罪犯的意思 长官
I don't think criminals, sir.
不是
No.
有医生 音乐家...
Doctors, musicians.
裁缝、职员、农夫、知识分子 我的意思是 普通老百姓
Tailors, clerks. Farmers, intellectuals. I mean, normal people.
犹太人
Juden, Juden.
Juden.
他们是犹太人
They're Jews.
波兰人跟吉普赛人
Poles and gypsies.
李高特?
Liebgott?
妇女集中营在下一个火车站
The women's camp is at the next railroad stop.
嘿 贝比 过来这里
Hey, Babe, come here.
看他们的手臂
Look at their arms.
跟牲口一样
Like cattle.
可恶
Goddamn.
老天爷
Ah, Jesus.
欧基夫?
O'Keefe?
我要打电话给辛克上校
I'm gonna call Sink.
叫史毕尔想办法给他们弄些食物...
Find Speirs and figure out how the hell to get them some food...
还有水
...and water.
我们走 速度加快点
Let's go, let's pick up the pace, come on.
马丁中士
Sergeant Martin...
把能装上小卡车的想办法弄来
...get what fits on the deuce and a half.
快 我们走!
Move, let's move.
闭嘴
Shut up.
把所有东西都拿走
Take everything, take it all.
到后面看看...闭嘴!
Check the back and shut up!
到后面看看还有没有东西可以...
Check the back and see if there's any kind of...
闭嘴!
Shut up!
我叫你闭嘴 你这个纳粹王八蛋!
I said shut up, you Nazi fuck!
你不是纳粹?
You're not a Nazi?
那是我搞错了? 你这个死肥走狗?
My mistake, you fat fucking prick.
那人呢? 你算是人吗?
How about a human being? Are you one of those?
或者是你要告诉我 你从没闻到那股尸臭味?
Or will you tell me you never smelled the fucking stench?
放了他
Let him go, Web.
他说他听不懂你在说什么
He says he doesn't know what the hell you're talking about.
狗屁
Bullshit.
泰伯特军士长 这真是混乱
Sergeant Talbert, this is chaos.
别急 每一个人都有份
There's plenty to go around, please.
还有更多的水会送来
We've got more water on the way.
迪克! 温特斯少校
Dick, Major Winters.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
长官
Sir.
这位是肯特医官 团部的外科大夫
This is Doctor Kent, the regimental surgeon.
医生 把你刚告诉我的 去告诉温特斯少校和尼克森上尉
Doc, tell Major Winters and Captain Nixon what you just told me.
我们得立刻停止供应这些人食物
Yes, sir. We need to stop giving these men food right now.
他们处于饥饿状态
They're starving.
如果我们太快给他们吃太多东西
If they eat too much too quickly...
反而会导致他们死亡
...they'll eat themselves to death.
我们需要将他们留在营内
We need to keep them here...
直到在镇上找到他们栖身之处
...till we can find a place for them in town.
你要我们把这些人再关回去?
You want us to lock these people back up?
我们别无选择 尼克
We got no choice, Nix.
不然他们会四处分散
Otherwise they might scatter.
我们需要将他们集中起来
We must keep them centralized...
以便监督他们的食物摄取跟医疗
...to supervise their food intake and medical treatment.
所以在我们找到更好的地方之前
So, until we find some place better...
辛克上校
Colonel Sink.
这真是不得已的 就这么办吧
It's a crying ass shame, but let's get it done.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
我跟你们一样不愿意
I don't like it any more than you guys.
泰勒将军?
General Taylor?
我是506团的鲍伯・辛克
Bob Sink, 506.
长官 我们在...蓝德斯堡
Sir, we're on, we're at Landsberg...
布克洛的另一头
...the other side of Buchloe.
我们发现了些你应该要来看看的东西 长官
We found something I believe you ought to see, sir.
我没有办法跟他们说 长官
I can't tell them that, sir.
非说不可 乔
You've got to, Joe.
好吧 长官
Yes, sir.
格兰特 克里斯登生
Grant, Christenson.
这些人犯必须马上回集中营
The prisoners must be put back in the camp immediately.
去告诉大家
Let the men know.
搞了半天 结果我住在全德国唯一没有酒喝的房子
Turns out I'm staying in the only dry frigging house in Germany.
我还以为你不喝当地的酒
Thought you weren't drinking the local.
管他的
Yeah, well.
我听到师部发来的消息
Heard from Division.
到处不断发现象这样的集中营
Been finding camps like this all over the place.
老天
Jesus.
俄国人好象找到一个更悲惨的
Seems the Russians liberated one a lot worse.
更惨?
Worse?
对
Yeah.
似乎是这样
Apparently.
比这个还大上十倍
Ten times as big.
有毒气室 火炉
Execution chambers, ovens.
是用来焚化尸体的
For cremating all the bodies.
老天啊
Jesus.
当地居民都说他们从不知道集中营的存在
The locals claim that they never even knew the camp existed.
他们都说我们太夸张了
They say we're exaggerating.
明天他们就要来个震撼教育
Well, they're gonna have a hell of an education tomorrow.
泰勒将军大约在一小时前宣布了戒严令
General Taylor declared martial law about an hour ago.
命令全镇年龄14到80岁之间的健康镇民开始帮忙埋葬尸体
Ordered every able-bodied German in town aged 14 to 80, to start burying the bodies.
明天早上开始
That'll begin in the morning.
第十装甲师会监督清理工作
10th Armored are gonna supervise cleanup.
那我们呢?
What about us?
我们向达兰...塔兰出发
We head out for Thalheim, Thalheim, tomorrow.
明天中午十二点
1200 hours.
要不要手帕 长官?
Kerchief, sir?
什么?
What?
不用了 谢谢
No, thanks.
向前移
Move along.
放到那里
Over there.
别停 继续挖
Don't stop. Keep digging.
你们俩 快点
You, too. Come on.
希特勒死了
Hitler's dead.
天啊
Holy shit.
在柏林举枪自尽了
Shot himself in Berlin.
战争结束了吗 长官?
Is the war over, sir?
还没有
No.
我们奉命前往贝希特斯佳登
We have orders to Berchtesgaden.
一个小时内出发
We're gonna move out in one hour.
为什么? 主人不是死了吗?
Why, the man's not home?
他三年前就该自杀了
Should've killed himself three years ago.
那就会省我们许多麻烦
Saved us a lot of trouble.
对 他早该如此...
Yeah, he should've...
可惜他没有
...but he didn't.
在接下来的几个月里
盟军陆续发现无数的战犯集中营跟死亡营区
这些营区都是纳粹分子面对...
所谓"犹太人问题"的最后解决办法
在1942到1945年之间有五百万少数民族
及六百万犹太人遭到屠杀
大部分都发生在集中营里